post-install.com 2014-06-17

# Privacy Policy - post-install.com

### Privacy Policy for post-install.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@post-install.com.

At post-install.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by postdownload. net and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, post-install.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files may include but is not limited to internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Int ernet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic infor mation. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

post-install.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on vi sitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on post-install.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP addre ss when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

post-install.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain pra ctices. post-install.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
